ic4uae.com 2013-05-21

# Carrefour :: IC4UAE

  * Home
  * /
  * Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

#### 1 Introduction

Carrefour Hypermarkets LLC ("[Company]") takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes how and why we obtain, store and process data which can identify you. We may use personal information we collect from you to send you further information on our products and services or to keep you up to date on our promotional offers by post, courier or email. We may also disclose this information to approved third parties for the purposes of administering any warranty plans or providing you with details of goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you don't like the sound of that there's a simple unsubscribe link in every email we send. Alternatively you can email our customer Information centre at[ info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com ](mailto:info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com) to request that your details are removed. Please be aware that in order to improve our service, we may use personal information that we collect about you to carry out market research. We may update this policy from time to time and shall indicate on the web site when changes have been made.

#### 2 The Information we collect 

Information is collected from you when you register with us, or when you contribute to or use some of the advanced features on the site. The information we collect is clearly set out on the web page on which we collect it. See for example our registration page and Cart Checkout section. In addition, we may collect your IP address and use cookies unless you configure your web browser not to accept them.

#### Cookies 

A "cookie" is a small file stored on your machine that includes information to help you shop online. There's absolutely nothing sinister about cookies - all they do is make web shopping easier. For example, when you're ready to purchase an item, a cookie allows our site to "remember" that you've added it to your basket. You'll need to have cookies enabled in order to buy anything from our site. If you'd like to learn more about cookies just go to [www.allaboutcookies.org ](http://www.ic4uae.com/Pages/www.allaboutcookies.org)

#### 3 Why we collect it 

We collect information about you so that we can personalise your use of the site, assist your use of the site and improve the site generally. Depending upon your selections for our data protection questions we may arrange for you to be sent information about related products and services from us and carefully selected third parties (see section 4). You may update the answers to your questions at any time. 

#### 4 Who we disclose it to 

4.1 We will only pass on information about you as an individual (as opposed to aggregate information) to third parties to enable us to perform services requested by you or with your prior consent. 

4.2 If you give your consent, we will pass your contact details to third parties who may then occasionally send communications to you to provide information, offers and services that may be of interest to you. 

4.3 In certain circumstances we may need to disclose information about you if you breach this privacy policy or if you breach the Terms and Conditions. We may also disclose or access your account if required to do so by law or by any Governmental body. 

4.4 We will only pass on information about you as an individual (as opposed to aggregate information) to third parties overseas to enable us to perform services requested by you.

#### 5 Security 

Keeping information about you secure is very important to us and certain sections of the site may encrypt data using SSL or a comparable standard. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. As a result, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

#### 6 Automated decisions 

Parts of www.iC4uae.com and our billing process (which is transacted via Emirates NBD) are automatic and we may process your personal data as part of the billing process. 

#### 7 Accessing and updating your personal information 

We will always let you have a copy of personal information we have about you, should you request it, and you may correct it if you wish. Instructions about how to do this are available from [info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com](mailto:info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com)

#### 8 Questions? 

If you have any questions or complaints relating to this Privacy Policy or how we use the personal information we have about you, please contact [ info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com](mailto:info.webstore@mafcarrefour.com) We will endeavour to respond to you promptly.
